webstagram.biz 2019-12-30

# Privacy Policy - Webstagram

Thank you for visiting Webstagram. Please make sure to read this privacy policy very carefully before you use the Webstagram. If you do not agree with any of it, please do not use our Webstagram. By using or accessing the Webstagram, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

At Webstagram we value the privacy of our users and it’s important for us that you understand what happens to the information you provide to us. This document is to help you understand how we use, store, collect and disclose your data. 

#### Collection of Information

You are free to browse this Webstagram without revealing any personal information making it possible to identify you. However, once you have sent us your identifiable personal information, you are no longer anonymous to us. We collect two types of information from Users/Organizers of the Webstagram: “Automatic Anonymous Information” and “Identifiable Personal Information”. 

#### Automatic Anonymous Information

The Webstagram/Contest Tool make it possible to monitor certain information automatically, based on your behaviour. This information does not identify you personally. We use this information to improve the Content and functionality of the Webstagram/Contest Tool, and to better understand and satisfy our visitors. This information may include the browser you use, your IP address or other information. This information is referred to herein as the AAI. 

####  Identifiable Personal Information (IPI) 

IPI is individually identifiable information about you that allows us to identify or contact you. Some of the Webstagram’s functions require asking you for certain IPI, such as your instagram username, instagram password and/or other personal information. 

But we do not handle your Instagram passwords directly. We use Instagram's API and OAuth 2.0 protocol to authorize Our users. Our databases are secured with passwords to guard against unauthorized access of Our systems. Only engineer staff members may access data on a need-to-know basis. 

You may choose to provide IPI in order to access certain functions on the Webstagram. You can always choose not to provide certain information, but in that case it may be that you cannot use certain of the Webstagram’s functions. 

####  Sharing of Information to third parties 

The Webstagram will target advertising based on personal information provided by users and inferred from Webstagram usage. This may include gender, age, or geographic data. Webstagram does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. We may bundle and share the non-personal information we collect from you and other users with advertisers, third parties, trusted partners and affiliates so that they display advertising that better suits your interests. We may aggregate your PII with information about others. In that case we will make your information non-personally identifiable by removing your name and other characteristics that would identify it as you. We may use and/or share the resulting non-PII with third parties. We may provide some non-personal information to others who help us understand how you use the Webstagram. 

####  Sharing and Disclosure of Information to any authority parties 

We may be required by law enforcement, government administrators, and/or judicial authorities to provide personally identifiable information. We will disclose personally identifiable information upon receipt of a court order, or if required to co-operate with law enforcement, administrative or other governmental agencies. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that We in good faith believe to be unlawful. 

#### Do we use 'cookies'? 

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

#### We use cookies to: 

Keep track of advertisements.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It won't affect the users experience that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. 

However, you can still place orders.

#### How do we protect visitor information? 

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

We use an SSL certificate.  
We only provide articles and information, and we never ask for personal or private information. 

####  Connecting With Social Media. 

When sign in to your Webstagram account through instagram, you are allowing us to have access to both PII and non-PII from your social media profile. That PII may be publicly viewed and may possibly be used by other members of these Webstagram's. 

####  Changing of Our Policy

This Privacy Policy is subject to change at anytime. You should periodically check back and review this Privacy Policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and with whom we share it. 

#### Commenting or posting on the Webstagram

When you post information (a tag, a link, a comment…) on the Webstagram, the information may be consulted or used by any User; we therefore invite you to take care when posting, as this can lead to you receiving unsolicited information from Users. 

#### Links

On the Webstagram you will find various links directing you to Third Party Webstagram or to Third Party Content. Webstagram shall not be liable for the links posted by Users or the privacy policies of such third parties. This Privacy Policy, do not govern to Third Party Webstagram or to Third Party Content which the User accesses from the Webstagram. 

#### Contact

For any questions concerning this Privacy Policy, other policies for the Webstagram or how to use the Webstagram, [please contact us. ](https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSerRrVkK5ZT0mf04CPf-e07dPBQJaAeC_nDGOia1jYXB3K4QA/viewform?usp=sf_link)
